CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
COLUMBIA TRISTAR
DOMESTIC TELEVISION
NEVER LIKED THE CHECK AT
THE END OF THE MEAL SYSTEM.
MONEY'S DIFFERENT
BEFORE AND AFTER YOU EAT.
BEFORE YOU EAT,
MONEY HAS NO VALUE.
YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT MONEY
WHEN YOU'RE HUNGRY.
YOU'RE LIKE THE RULER
OF AN EMPIRE--MORE DRINKS!
APPETIZERS!
QUICKLY, QUICKLY.
IT WILL BE THE GREATEST
MEAL OF OUR LIVES.
THEN AFTER THE MEAL, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT THE PANTS OPEN,
YOU GOT
THE NAPKINS DESTROYED,
CIGARETTE BUTT
IN THE MASHED POTATOES.
THEN THE CHECK COMES
AT THAT MOMENT.
PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS UPSET,
YOU KNOW.
THEY'RE MYSTIFIED
BY THE CHECK.
WHAT IS THIS?
HOW COULD THIS BE?
THEY START PASSING IT
AROUND THE TABLE.
DOES THIS LOOK
RIGHT TO YOU?
WE'RE NOT HUNGRY NOW.
WHY ARE WE BUYING
ALL THIS FOOD?
I THINK SUPERMAN
PROBABLY HAS A VERY
GOOD SENSE OF HUMOR.
I NEVER HEARD HIM
SAY ANYTHING FUNNY.
IT'S COMMON SENSE.
HE'S GOT SUPER STRENGTH,
SUPER SPEED.
I'M SURE HE'S GOT
SUPER HUMOR.
YOU'D THINK THAT,
BUT EITHER YOU'RE
BORN WITH HUMOR
OR YOU'RE NOT.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE.
EVEN AFTER GOING
FROM THE RED SUN
OF KRYPTON
TO THE YELLOW SUN
OF EARTH.
WHY? WHY WOULD THAT
ONE AREA OF HIS MIND
NOT BE AFFECTED BY
THE YELLOW SUN OF EARTH?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE AIN'T FUNNY.
HI. I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
NO PROBLEM.
I DROPPED A GRAPE.
WHAT?
I DROPPED A GRAPE
IN THE KITCHEN,
AND IT DISAPPEARED.
I COULDN'T FIND IT.
I WAS ON MY KNEES
FOR 10 MINUTES
LOOKING FOR
THIS STUPID GRAPE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WH-WHERE IT WENT.
WERE YOU CRYING?
I MEAN, IT'S JUST
A GRAPE.
YOU'LL FIND IT.
NO. I'M JUST GETTING OVER
AN ALLERGY ATTACK.
THIS GUY I'M
GOING OUT WITH--
ROBERT.
YES. THANK YOU.
HE HAS TWO CATS,
AND I'M ALLERGIC TO THEM.
YOU KNOW, I FINALLY
MEET A NORMAL MAN,
AND I CAN'T EVEN GO
INTO HIS APARTMENT.
OF COURSE MY APARTMENT
IS THE ACTORS' STUDIO,
SO WE CAN'T GO THERE.
IT'S CAUSING A LOT OF
PROBLEMS, YOU KNOW?
HE WON'T EVEN LEAVE
HIS CATS FOR THE WEEKEND.
GUYS WITH CATS--
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M CONSIDERING
ASKING THIS GIRL
I'M SEEING--
VANESSA?
VANESSA. THANK YOU.
I'M CONSIDERING
ASKING HER TO GO
AWAY A COUPLE DAYS.
OH, NO.
I'D HAVE TO
ADVISE
AGAINST THAT.
WHAT DO YOU
KNOW THIS WOMAN,
A MONTH?
YOU'LL BE
TOGETHER
72 HOURS.
THAT'S
A DATING
DECATHLON.
WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE HER TO THAT
PLACE IN VERMONT?
IT'S REALLY CHARMING--
WITH SEPARATE FAUCETS
FOR THE HOT AND COLD.
SHE'LL LOVE IT.
THAT'S EXQUISITE.
LISTEN, IF IT'S NOT
TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
COULD YOU PASS ME
THAT PAPER
OVER THERE?
JUST THE BUSINESS
SECTION.
YOU BETTER
FIND THAT GRAPE
BEFORE IT MUTATES
INTO ANOTHER LIFE FORM.
THERE WAS ONCE
A MUTANT GRAPE
THAT TERRORIZED
AN ENTIRE TOWN
IN THE TEXAS PANHANDLE.
THEY BROUGHT IN
THE ARMY.
NOBODY COULD STOP IT.
APPARENTLY, IT HAD
A PIT OF STEEL.
UP AGAIN.
THIS IS
INCREDIBLE.
I'M--I'M
GETTING IT.
GETTING WHAT?
A STOCK.
WHAT STOCK?
YOU EVER MEET
SIMONS?
MAYBE.
HIS FRIEND
WILKENSON
MADE A FORTUNE
IN THE MARKET.
HE'S GOT
SOME NEW THING--
A BIG MERGER.
I WASN'T EVEN
SUPPOSED TO
SAY ANYTHING.
YOU SHOULD
CONSIDER THIS.
HOW HIGH'S IT
SUPPOSED TO GO?
SIMONS SAID
WILKENSON
WOULD TELL ME
THE EXACT
MINUTE TO SELL.
YOU WANT TO
DO IT?
BOY, I DON'T KNOW.
I GOT NO MONEY.
WHAT KIND OF COMPANY?
IT'S CALLED
CENTRAX.
THEY GOT
SOME NEW
TECHNIQUE
FOR TELEVISING
OPERA.
TELEVISING OPERA?
SOME SORT OF
ELECTRONIC THINGY.
HOW MUCH
YOU INVESTING?
5,000.
10. 10,000.
BOY.
COME ON.
WILKENSON'S
GOT MILLIONS
INVESTED
IN THIS STOCK.
IT'S GONE UP
3 POINTS
WHILE I'VE
WATCHED IT.
WHAT IF I LOSE IT?
COME ON!
TAKE 2,500.
WE'LL DO IT
TOGETHER.
COME ON!
WE'RE IN IT
TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT. 2,500.
THAT'S IT.
CAN I TAKE
YOUR ORDER?
I'LL CHECK
TO THE RAISER.
MY BET?
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL OPEN WITH
A TUNA SANDWICH.
TUNA?
OH, THE DOLPHIN THING?
THEY'RE DYING
IN THE NETS.
YOU KNOW, THE WHOLE
CONCEPT OF LUNCH
IS BASED ON TUNA.
JERRY, CAN'T YOU
INCORPORATE
ONE UNSELFISH ACT
IN YOUR DAILY ROUTINE?
WHEN I'M DRIVING, I LET
PEOPLE IN ALL THE TIME.
I'M ALWAYS WAVING
EVERYBODY IN.
GO AHEAD. GO AHEAD.
GO AHEAD.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL HAVE
THE CHICKEN SALAD.
UM, AND I'M
GOING TO HAVE
AN ENGLISH MUFFIN,
MARGARINE ON THE SIDE,
AND COFFEE.
AND YOU?
I'LL HAVE THE TUNA.
THOSE PEOPLE
TALKING BEHIND US
RUINED THAT MOVIE FOR ME.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
DO SOMETHING?
WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO DO?
I GAVE THE GUY
THE HALF TURN.
THEN I GAVE HIM
THE FULL TURN
WITH THE EYE ROLL.
BEYOND THAT,
I'M RISKING A PUNCH
IN THE MOUTH.
EXCUSE ME. DO YOU HAVE
THESE IN THE PUFFS?
NO PUFFS.
JUST FLAKES.
HAVE YOU
THOUGHT ANY MORE
ABOUT THAT TRIP?
YEAH. I'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT IT.
I HEARD ABOUT
THIS GREAT PLACE
IN VERMONT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M WORRIED
ABOUT IT.
IT'S LOTS
OF PRESSURE.
IT'S GREAT. IT SPEEDS UP
THE INTIMACY LEVEL.
IT'S LIKE PUTTING
THE RELATIONSHIP
IN A TIME COMPRESSOR.
WHERE WE'D BE
IN SIX MONTHS,
WE'D ACCOMPLISH
IN THREE DAYS.
OH. SO YOU WANT TO
MOVE OUR RELATIONSHIP
INTO PHASE TWO.
EXACTLY.
I LOVE PHASE TWO.
EXTRA TOOTHBRUSHES,
INCREASED
PHONE CALL FREQUENCY...
WALKING AROUND NAKED.
YOU KNOW, THE PRESENTS
GET BETTER IN PHASE TWO.
REALLY?
CAN WE GO
FISHING UP THERE?
WE CAN FISH--WHAT,
BLUES, CARP...MARLIN?
MARLIN IN VERMONT?
OH, BIG
FIGHTING MARLIN.
JERRY,
THE STOCK'S
THE SAME AS WHEN
YOU CHECKED EARLIER.
THERE ARE NO CHANGES
AFTER THE MARKET CLOSES.
THE STOCK'S STILL DOWN.
BUT THIS IS
A DIFFERENT PAPER.
I THOUGHT
MAYBE THEY HAVE
DIFFERENT SOURCES.
[IMITATES AUTOMOBILE]
IS THAT MY PAPER?
BAD NEWS, MY FRIEND.
WHAT NEWS?
CENTRAX.
OH, COME ON.
IT'S DOWN AGAIN?
2 1/2 POINTS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
LET ME SEE THAT.
WHOO.
THAT'S 4 1/2 POINTS
IN 3 DAYS.
THAT'S ALMOST
HALF MY MONEY.
HEY, I TOLD YOU.
YEAH. YOU TOLD ME.
IT'S ALL MANIPULATED
WITH JUNK BONDS.
YOU CAN'T WIN.
ONE THING
I DON'T UNDERSTAND--
WHY DOES IT PLEASE YOU?
GEORGE COSTANZA,
PLEASE.
I'M JUST SAYING
DUMP THAT STOCK NOW!
GEORGE,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SELL IT!
JUST SAY SELL IT!
WHERE IS THE GUY?
NOTHING? ALMOST
HALF MY MONEY'S GONE.
WELL, CALL ME RIGHT BACK.
NOBODY CAN REACH WILKENSON.
HE HASN'T BEEN HEARD
FROM IN THREE DAYS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU PUT YOUR MONEY
IN CENTRAX.
YOU COULD HAVE
INVESTED
IN MY ROLL-OUT
TIE DISPENSER.
THE ROLL-OUT
WHAT WAS THAT ONE?
YOU'RE IN A RESTAURANT.
THERE'S A VERY BIG
MEETING COMING UP.
OH, MAN.
MUSTARD ON YOUR TIE.
OH, NO!
YOU JUST TEAR IT OFF
AND--WHOOP--
YOU GOT A NEW ONE
RIGHT HERE.
THEN...YOU'RE GONE.
YOU'RE GONE, ALL RIGHT.
WHERE YOU GOING?
YOU TAKING A TRIP?
YEAH. I'M GOING
TO VERMONT WITH VANESSA.
CAN I USE YOUR PLACE?
I GOT FRIENDS
VISITING THIS WEEKEND.
WHAT FRIENDS?
JUST SOME PEOPLE I MET
AT A ROCK CONCERT.
MIND IF THEY USE YOUR BED?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
THEY'RE REALLY
GOOD PEOPLE, JERRY.
YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE ANARCHISTS.
THEY'RE--THEY'RE HUGE.
GEORGE, WHAT?
YOU'RE KIDDING.
WELL, WHAT'S WRONG?
SO WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO?
GREAT. I'LL SPEAK
TO YOU LATER.
WILKENSON--HE'S
SUPPOSED TO TELL US
WHEN TO SELL--
HE'S IN
THE HOSPITAL.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG?
SIMONS
JUST SAID HE'S
IN THE HOSPITAL.
OK. FINE.
HAS SIMONS BEEN IN TOUCH?
OF COURSE. HE
LEFT TWO MESSAGES.
HE JUST HASN'T
HEARD BACK YET,
THAT'S ALL.
THAT'S IT.
I'M SELLING.
JUST GIVE IT
A LITTLE MORE TIME.
I SHOULDN'T
HAVE DONE THIS.
I'M A WRECK.
I'M NOT CUT OUT
FOR INVESTING.
THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING THERE.
WHERE?
TO THE HOSPITAL.
THE HOSPITAL?
I'LL FIND OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
ARE YOU NUTS?
YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW THE GUY.
SO WHAT?
I'LL START TALKING,
CASUALLY,
AND WORK MY WAY
AROUND TO IT.
WHAT IF HE'S
IN AN IRON LUNG?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
HOW YOU FEELING,
MR. WILKENSON?
SHHHHH.
BY THE WAY,
WHAT'S HAPPENING
WITH CENTRAX?
MAYBE HE'S THERE
RESTING.
WHO GOES TO A HOSPITAL
TO REST?
WHAT ARE YOU,
A DOCTOR?
OK. FINE. FINE.
WHEN ARE YOU GOING?
TODAY.
I'M GOING TODAY.
DON'T DO
ANYTHING
UNTIL I RETURN.
ALL RIGHT.
BOY, I HAVE TO
GET TO A BATHROOM.
MAY I HELP YOU?
I PICKED UP THIS
SHIRT YESTERDAY.
IT'S COMPLETELY
SHRUNK.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY
NO WAY I CAN
WEAR IT.
WHEN DID YOU
BRING IT HERE?
WHAT'S
THE DIFFERENCE?
YOU SEE
THE SIZE OF THIS?
YOU GOT A RECEIPT?
I CAN'T FIND
THE RECEIPT.
YOU SHOULD
GET THE RECEIPT.
FORGET ABOUT
THE RECEIPT.
EVEN IF I HAD
THE RECEIPT,
LOOK AT IT.
IT'S A HAND PUPPET.
WHAT AM I GOING TO
DO WITH THIS?
YES, BUT HOW DO I KNOW
WE DID THE SHIRT?
YOU THINK THIS IS
A SCAM I HAVE?
I TAKE THIS SHIRT
ALL OVER THE CITY,
CONNING DRY CLEANERS
OUT OF MONEY?
FORGET MONEY. I DON'T
EVEN WANT THE MONEY.
JUST ONCE
I'D LIKE TO HEAR
A DRY CLEANER ADMIT
THAT SOMETHING
WAS THEIR FAULT.
THAT'S IT.
I WANT AN ADMISSION
OF GUILT.
MAYBE YOU ASKED FOR IT
TO BE WASHED.
NO. DRY-CLEANED.
LET ME EXPLAIN
TO YOU SOMETHING.
CERTAIN TYPES OF FABRICS,
DIFFERENT CHEMICALS
CAN REACT,
CAUSING--
YOU SHRUNK IT.
YOU KNOW YOU
SHRUNK IT.
JUST TELL ME
YOU SHRUNK IT.
I SHRUNK IT.
AH-CHOO!
BLESS YOU.
THANK YOU.
WHAT EVIDENCE IS THERE
THAT CATS ARE SO SMART
ANYWAY, HUH?
WHAT DO THEY DO?
BECAUSE THEY'RE CLEAN?
I'M SORRY.
MY UNCLE PETE SHOWERS
FOUR TIMES A DAY,
AND HE CAN'T COUNT TO 10.
DON'T GIVE ME HYGIENE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T THINK
OF ANY SOLUTION.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
THEY SHOULD MEET
WITH SOME
UNFORTUNATE ACCIDENT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
A HIT MAN WOULD CHARGE
TO RUB OUT
A COUPLE OF CATS?
WELL, IT COULDN'T BE
TOO EXPENSIVE.
13, 14 BUCKS A CAT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK,
JERRY?
WANT TO MAKE 28 BUCKS?
I'M NO CAT KILLER.
HOW ABOUT WE GO
OVER THERE RIGHT NOW
AND WE SHAVE THEM?
I'D REALLY
LIKE TO GO, ELAINE,
BUT...GEORGE
IS COMING BACK
FROM THE HOSPITAL.
I GOT TO
WAIT FOR HIM.
BUT OTHERWISE,
I WOULD
DEFINITELY GO.
HE ACTUALLY WENT
TO THE HOSPITAL?
YEAH.
MAN, HE'S NUTS.
YEAH, HE'S NUTS.
YOU WANT TO BUMP OFF
A COUPLE OF CATS.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S DOWN AGAIN.
HOW MUCH YOU DOWN
ALTOGETHER?
I DON'T KNOW.
$1,500?
WOW.
YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SAY WOW.
I KNOW IT'S WOW.
AND THERE'S
THAT SMILE AGAIN.
WHAT IS THAT?
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
IT'S GEORGE.
OH, LOOK AT THIS ONE
BY THE BUS STOP.
JERRY, COME HERE.
TAKE A LOOK.
I REALLY DON'T
NEED TO LOOK.
WHAT A BODY.
YEAH.
THAT'S FOR ME.
AND YOU'RE JUST WHAT
SHE'S LOOKING FOR, TOO.
STRANGER LEERING THROUGH
A PAIR OF BINOCULARS
TEN FLOORS UP.
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN THERE
AND TRY TALKING TO HER.
[SNAP]
WHAT?
DID YOU
GO DOWN THERE?
DID HE TELL YOU
WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN?
HOW LONG
WERE YOU THERE?
15 SECONDS.
YOU TOLD HIM
YOU KNEW SIMONS.
I MENTIONED SIMONS.
NEXT THING I KNOW,
I'M IN THE PARKING LOT!
PERHAPS THEY HAD
SOME SORT OF
A FALLING OUT.
I'LL TELL YOU
ONE THING--
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE'S GOT,
BUT FOR A SICK GUY,
HE'S VERY STRONG.
WELL, THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING
TO VERMONT.
I'M NOT THINKING
ABOUT THIS.
I'M SELLING.
DIDN'T WORK, HUH?
HEH HEH. NOT QUITE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO ABOUT THE STOCK?
I'M KEEPING IT.
I'M GOING DOWN
WITH THE SHIP.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I'M GETTING
ALL MY SNEAKERS
AT A DISCOUNT NOW.
I KNOW.
YOU MENTIONED IT.
OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
GOD, GET ME OUT OF HERE.
WHAT A MISTAKE!
WHAT MADE ME THINK
THIS WOULD WORK?
AND I'VE STILL GOT
ANOTHER DAY!
I'VE GOT
NOTHING LEFT TO SAY.
WAIT, WAIT.
I'VE GOT ONE.
THAT'S A NICE WATCH.
YEAH.
DO YOU WIND IT?
NO. IT'S GOT
A LITTLE BATTERY.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
THE DRIVE HOME
SHOULD BE A DELIGHT.
I'M SPEEDING THE WHOLE WAY.
LET 'EM THROW ME IN JAIL.
I DON'T CARE.
THAT'S THE MANAGER.
WANT ME TO SEE ABOUT
ANOTHER ROOM?
NO. IT'S OK.
SO YOU DON'T FIND
THE SEPARATE HOT AND COLD
FAUCETS CHARMING?
NOT ESPECIALLY.
WHAT SHALL WE
DO THIS AFTERNOON?
WHAT CAN WE DO?
IT'S RAINING.
WE COULD PLAY SORRY.
WE COULD PLAY
STEAL THE OLD
MAN'S BUNDLE.
MAYBE I CAN GET
AN EXTENSION CORD
AND HANG MYSELF.
WHAT KIND OF PERFUME
IS THAT YOU'RE WEARING?
OH, YOU'VE NEVER
HEARD OF IT.
NO. WHAT KIND IS IT?
I CAN'T TELL YOU.
YEAH, THAT'S REAL NORMAL.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
COULD I SEE YOUR
BUSINESS SECTION?
THE STOCK?
THANK YOU.
THOUGHT YOU
GOT OUT OF THAT.
I DID.
I'M JUST CURIOUS.
IT'S BEEN ALMOST A WEEK.
I WANT TO CHECK IT OUT.
6 POINTS?
IT'S UP 6 POINTS.
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO SELL.
YOU DID NOT TELL ME
I SAID THE MARKET
FLUCTUATES. REMEMBER?
LOOK, VANESSA,
OF COURSE THE MARKET
FLUCTUATES.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
I JUST GOT FLUCTUATED
OUT OF $4,000.
THAT'S PROBABLY
WHY WE'RE...
WHAT?
FORGET IT.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY...
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY
WE'RE STAYING HERE--
YOU LOST MONEY
ON THE STOCK.
SO, WHAT AM I
LOOKING AT HERE?
29 HOURS TO GO?
WELL, AT LEAST I GOT
PLENTY OF TIME
TO FIND OUT THE NAME
OF THAT PERFUME.
JAMES, HE KILLS ME.
HAVE SOMETHING ELSE.
HAVE SOME DESSERT.
I'M GOOD, THANKS.
ELAINE, GET SOMETHING.
IT'S ALL TAKEN CARE OF.
I'M KIND OF
FULL.
SO DON'T FINISH IT!
SHE'S FULL.
SO, BIG DADDY,
I'M JUST CURIOUS.
HOW MUCH DID YOU CLEAR
ON YOUR LITTLE
TRANSACTION ALL TOLD?
I DON'T LIKE TO
DISCUSS FIGURES.
HOW MUCH?
I DON'T KNOW--8,000.
IT'S A HYUNDAI.
GET OUT OF HERE.
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO SELL.
SIMONS MADE MONEY,
WILKENSON
CLEANED UP.
SO WILKENSON'S
OUT OF THE HOSPITAL?
NO.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED.
YOU DON'T RECOVER
THAT QUICKLY
FROM A NOSE JOB.
AH-CHOO!
IS THAT STILL
FROM THOSE CATS?
NO--UGH--I JUST
GOT A COLD.
WHAT EVER HAPPENED
WITH THAT?
I GAVE HIM AN ULTIMATUM.
HE CHOSE THE CATS?
THEY'RE VERY
CLEAN ANIMALS.
I GOT TO SAY,
THAT'S PRETTY BAD
LOSING OUT TO A CAT.
ALMOST AS BAD
AS LOSING OUT
TO A PERFUME.
TOLD YOU THOSE TRIPS
ARE RELATIONSHIP KILLERS.
TOO BAD YOU
CAN'T GET SUPERMAN
TO FLY AROUND THE EARTH
AT SUPER SPEED
AND REVERSE TIME.
GET ALL THE MONEY BACK,
AVOID THE WHOLE TRIP
TO VERMONT...
SUPERMAN CAN
REVERSE TIME?
WE WENT OVER THAT.
PSST.
WILKENSON'S GOT A BITE
ON A NEW ONE.
THE TRAMCO CORPORATION
OUT OF, UH...
SPRINGFIELD, I THINK.
THEY'RE ABOUT TO
INTRODUCE SOME SORT
OF A ROBOT BUTCHER.
A ROBOT BUTCHER?
SHH.
IF YOU WANT TO GET IN--
VERY LITTLE TIME.
AHEM. SWEETHEART.
NO, NO, NO.
THAT OUGHT TO COVER IT.
JUST A SECOND.
JUST LET ME...PEEK.
GOOD.
COME ON!
COME ON, COME ON...
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
COLUMBIA TRISTAR
DOMESTIC TELEVISION
icap.org--
"YOUR MONEY SHOULD
WORK FOR YOU."
I'VE DECIDED
I'LL DO THE WORK,
I'LL LET
THE MONEY RELAX.
YOU KNOW?
YOU PUT
YOUR MONEY TO WORK,
A LOT OF TIMES,
IT GETS FIRED.
WHAT HAPPENED?
MY MONEY WAS WORKING FOR ME.
YEAH, I REMEMBER
YOUR MONEY.
SHOWING UP LATE,
TAKING TIME OFF...
WE HAD TO LET HIM GO.